playphone.com 2018-08-20

# Mobile Game Developer Social Privacy Policy | PlayPhone Inc

We know how important your privacy is to you, so we have designed our social gaming network to protect information about you from unauthorized disclosure to others. This Playphone, Inc. ("Playphone") Privacy Policy details how we collect, use, and in certain circumstances, share your information, including your personal information:

\- When you use our social gaming network on your phone or other device (the "Service");

\- When you use and interact with Playphone's applications or games (the "Apps");

\- Online at playphone.com or any other site operated by Playphone (the "Sites"); and

\- When you call, email or otherwise communicate with Playphone.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to games or other applications from third-parties that may be available through the Service (our "Partners") and does not apply to game portals Playphone has developed specifically for wireless providers, e.g., Verizon Games.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and if you have any questions, feel free to contact us. By accessing the Service, Apps, or Sites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please note that we may modify the Privacy Policy from time to time. It is your responsibility to ensure that you regularly review our Privacy Policy, posted at www.playphone.com, as continued usage of the Service, Apps, or Sites indicates your acceptance of such modifications.

We collect and record the information you have provided. We may also collect your email address, as applicable, in accordance with the granted permissions on your Device. Other than names, phone numbers and email addresses, we don't generally collect any personally identifying information about our users, with the exception of any credit card, debit card, prepaid card, scratch card, gift card or other information provided by you for billing and payment purposes and Activity Information, described below. We may offer you the opportunity to submit other information about yourself (such as gender, age, occupation, hobbies, interests, location, etc.) or you may provide information through the Service or Apps. Such information shall also be covered by this Privacy Policy. Any actions you perform or information you provide that can be seen by other users of the Service, Apps, or Sites or any Partners, is considered public and should be performed and provided at your own risk and discretion.

When you use a social network service ("SNS") in connection with your use of the Service, we may record information regarding the use of that SNS and we may collect other information that is visible on the SNS in accordance with the relevant terms of use associated with the provider of the SNS.

Note that since some Playphone software is served through a SNS, it is your responsibility to read and accept the terms and privacy policy of such SNS prior to continuing. When you invite new members into your network, match contacts or send messages through the Service, we securely collect and maintain on secure servers the information associated with those messages, including email addresses, phone numbers and content.

The Service and Sites may contain links to other websites or services. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites or service. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Service or Site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site or application that collects personal information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Playphone on the Service, Sites, or in any Apps.

You should also be aware that most content delivered through the Service originates with another content provider. Such other content providers may place "cookies" on your browser, or otherwise gather information about you, including by asking you to provide information through the Service, Apps or Sites.

Finally, in order to provide the best possible service and to allow us to make certain internal reports and make recommendations, we automatically collect information about your use of the Service, Apps, or Sites, such as internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, other browser history, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time, or other similar information ("Activity Information").

By using the Service, you consent to our retaining all the above-described information in anonymous form as long as Playphone sees fit.

The Service is not directed at children, and Playphone does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register or participate in the Service or Apps. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Service or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to Playphone. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 we will take all reasonable measures to delete that information and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others or where required by law). If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at [help@playphone.com](mailto:help@playphone.com).

We do not sell, rent, or share your personally identifiable information ("personal information") to any third party, except as set forth below. We also may use certain information about you that is not personally identifiable.

We may use and share public information collected and your Activity Information to determine the kinds of content that you would like to view and to assist any advertisers in targeting their advertising.

We also use your name, email address, phone number and other information on our system to notify you of new product releases, service notifications, and to solicit your feedback and input. Those emails will contain links for preference management and where appropriate, unsubscribe links should you decide you do not want to receive further emails.

You understand and agree that we may access, preserve, and disclose any information we may have about you and the contents of your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to avoid liability, to comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, to protect our rights and property, or that of our affiliates or the public, or enforce this Privacy Policy or the Playphone End User Terms of Service (or any other applicable Playphone terms or policies). Playphone is not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that Playphone receives.

We also may use non-personally identifiable information and certain technical information about your phone, computer and your access of the Service (including your phone number and internet protocol address) in order to operate, maintain and manage the Service. 

Playphone may disclose information about you, including Activity Information, to its partners in order to provide the Service, Apps or Sites, resolve maintenance problems and correct errors in the Service, to communicate with you about the Service, Apps, or Sites, to provide you with advertising and promotional information in connection with the Service, Apps, or Sites and to enhance your experience with Playphone. However, we do not give our partners an independent right to share this information. For more information on automatic collection of information and advertising, see "Cookies" and "Third-party advertising companies," below.

Due to our contractual obligations with our Partners and other third parties and the need to share information to deliver and support the Service, we cannot provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of sharing information (whether personally identifiable information or other information) with these third parties.

Playphone, certain of its Partners, and each of their contractors and employees may view the information that you transmit to provide the Service, Apps, or Sites and otherwise perform the tasks set forth in this Privacy Policy.

You may decide to provide us with another person's email address so that person may be invited to join the Service or so that we may facilitate your communication with other people through the Service (such as when you upload an address book).

You may also provide us with another person's contact information for purposes of delivering information through a SNS. We use this information to contact and, if applicable, remind that person that he or she has been invited to join the Service or has received content through a SNS. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations from Playphone. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as set forth above. 

Playphone follows generally accepted industry security standards to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use your personal information. However, no commercial method of information transfer over the Internet or electronic data storage is known to be 100% secure. As a result, Playphone cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage in Playphone's systems. Be advised that if you send messages or post material containing personal information, that information may be collected and used by others.

Upon termination of your account, Playphone will remove your profile and other personal information from view. Playphone, however, may (but is not obligated to) keep information about you that is on its system following your termination, and this Privacy Policy will continue to apply to such information. Please contact Playphone if you have any questions about your personal information.

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Playphone or the acquisition of substantially all the assets of Playphone related to the business which collected such information, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, Playphone will notify users who have provided email addresses when information about those users is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

A cookie is a small text file recorded on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user and contains certain information about your particular login session and/or your use of the Service or Sites. The Service or Sites may send cookies to your computer when you access them, or otherwise view content through the Service, Apps or Sites. The Service and Sites use cookies to improve quality, make recommendations, and make the Service, Apps, or Sites easier to use for you. The "help" feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive new cookies or how to disable cookies altogether. If you reject cookies, you may not be able to participate in certain activities on the Services or Sites.

Playphone may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our Service, Apps, or Sites. Our advertisers may use third-party advertising technology to target interest-based advertising on the Service, Apps, or Sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your computer. Similarly, third-party advertising companies may provide us with pixel tags to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Pixel tags enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the site on which the beacon is located, and to learn which banner ads bring users to a given site.

Playphone does not otherwise provide any personally identifiable information to third-party advertising companies.

Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) has not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals and therefore, the Service and Sites do not recognize DNT.

If you want to withdraw consent to our use or storage of your personal information or which to opt-out from receiving email or other communications from Playphone, please send e-mail to [help@playphone.com](mailto:help@playphone.com). Recognize that withdrawing your consent may limit or preclude your use of the Service or Apps.

This Privacy Policy describes how we may share your information, including your personally identifiable information, for marketing and other purposes: "Use and sharing of your personal information." The Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Playphone Service, Apps, or Sites, including California residents.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to e-mail us at [help@playphone.com](mailto:help@playphone.com).
